DXE, we will deliver this payload into this Windows machine, so we have discussed a lot
of a lot of the methods, right, like 30-wheel bit serving PowerShell, CMD.exe and a lot
of a lot of that method we have discussed in previous sections, so we will use one of the
lot dash and we will deliver the payload, okay, so let me go to the lot dash, so we will
using this 30-wheel here, here you can find a 30-wheel URL cache dash split dash, this
is the parameter, we need to give to deliver the payload, okay, already we got a
control, so if you need the reverse connection, you can use the DRL injections or any other
cross injection method to do that, so I have used the DRL injection for this thing,
we have seen this previously, you can control a machine from here, right, so I can control
anything, so the privilege was a media mandatory level, so we will deliver our
method, how about set payload into the machine, okay, I will do one thing, let me redirect to one of the directory, go for features, so now we are in a
picture, so let me see, so how many executables are in features, so you can see a few executables in
pan or a retailer and all, so we will pull our antivirus.exe in here, we will use assertutil, so you can follow the same method they have used, okay,
that's URL gets dash split dash f, we need to give the URL here, so anyway our payload is
in our server directory, so if you are giving, so let me give you a small example, it
into 27 plus server, so here you can find our payload, so if I do the antivirus.exe, here the payload will be, let
me show you, so now you can see the period is automatically getting downloaded, right, antivirus.exe, okay, so we'll use dash f, and
we need to give the URL here, and we are going to save the file name as the same, and the virus.exe, so the
set it will stay, your cache command completed successfully, let me will very say whether the file was present under the
machine, so now you can see the antivirus.exe has been transferred successfully, here you can find the file,
in the Windows machine also, you can find the file, your antivirus.exe is here, so now you will execute
this antivirus.exe from here, so now I have run the antivirus.exe, so after running here you can see,
our cobalt site showing one of the machine, right, the V-count, right, so here you need to click on the
interact, rightly, interact, so now we can able to directly interact with the machine, okay, so now we got the
reverse connection from the, you know, cobalt site by executing this one, antivirus.exe, so you can control the
machine from here, okay, let me give the ps, if you do the help command, and cobalt site it will be listing a lot of
a lot of options here you can use, so there is a lot of options, okay, here you can use cobalt
site for a lot more things, I will check for what are the processes for running another machine, so process
lift, I am giving the ps, so it will take some time to get the result from the target
machine, we will pause this video till now, so now you can see the process, we have seen the
antivirus.exe communicating with the cobalt site, so let's stop of this video and we will continue
our discussion next video, see you guys, bye bye.